자신 스스로 보는것은 좋습니다.
Now, it would be great to see for
embeddings은 당신이 생각했던 것과 같이
clustering입니다.
yourself that these embeddings
are clustering together as you'd expect.
이것을 보는 하나의 방법은,
주어진 단어와 가장 근접한 단어를
One way to see it,
is by doing a nearest neighbor lookup
찾도록 가장 이웃한 것을 조회하보세요.
of the words that are closest
to any given word.
또 다른 방법은 2차원으로 embedding 공간을
줄이도록 해보고,
Another way is to try to reduce the
dimensionality of the embedding space
2차원 표현을 연결하는 것입니다.
down to two dimensions, and to plug
the two dimensional representation.
만약, 당신이 PCA와 같은
원시적인 방법을 수행한다면,
If you do that the native way, for
별 의미없는 결과가 나옵니다.
example using PCA,
you basically get a mush.
당신의 처리 과정에서 너무 많은
정보를 잃게 됩니다.
You lose too much
information in the process.
데이터의 이웃한 구조를 보존할 수 있는
투영 방법이 필요합니다.
What you need is a way of projecting
that preserves the neighborhood
structure of your data.
embedding space에서 유사한 단어는 인접하고
Things that are close in the embedding
space should remain close to the ends,
서로 멀리 있는것을 떨어져야 합니다.
things that are far should
be far away from each other.
t-SNE은 정확하게 수행하는 아주
효과적인 기술입니다.
One very effective technique that
does exactly that is called t-SNE.
시각화 기술로 실행할 수 있습니다.
You'll get to play with this
visualization technique in
the assignment